Guide to the Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature, 1936-2014 and undated RL.00045
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- United States, 1936-2014 and undated; 11; 52 boxes
  - Wisconsin, 227
    - General, 1962-1966 and undated (Box USA49)
    - General--Hotels, 1960s-2002 and undated (Box USA49)
    - General--Maps, 1979-1993 and undated (Box USA49)
    - General--Parks, 1986-1995 (Box USA50)
    - General--Sightseeing, 1968-2003 (Box USA50)
    - General--Travel guides, 1995-2002 (Box USA50)
    - Dells--General, 2001-2005; 2 folders (Box USA50)
    - Dells--Hotels, 1994-2003 and undated (Box USA50)
    - Dells--Theme parks, 1996-2002 and undated (Box USA50)
    - Door County--General, 1991-2004 (Box USA50)
    - Door County--Bailey's Harbor, 1994-2001 and undated (Box USA50)
    - Door County--Egg Harbor, 1960s-2001 and undated (Box USA50)
    - Door County--Ellison Bay, 1986-1991 and undated (Box USA50)
    - Door County--Ephraim, 1991-2002 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Door County--Fish Creek, 1991-1992 (Box USA51)
    - Door County--Sister Bay, 1991-1992 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Door County--Sturgeon Bay, 1980-1999 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Door County--Washington Island, 1992-1996 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Kohler/American Club, 1996-1999 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Lake Geneva, 1990-2002 and undated (Box USA51)
    - Milwaukee, 1985-2004 (Box USA51)
    - Spring Green, 1995-2001 and undated (Box USA51)
  - Wyoming, 228
    - General, 1970-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA51)
    - General--Maps, 1981-2002 (Box USA51)
    - General--Self-guided tours, undated (Box USA51)
    - Cody, 1974-1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA52)
    - Grand Teton, 1974-2003 and undated (Box USA52)
    - Jackson Hole--General, 1981-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA52)
    - Jackson Hole--Hotels, 1990-2005 and undated (Box USA52)
    - Jackson Hole--Hotels--Amangani, 2002-2005 (Box USA52)
    - Jackson Hole--Hotels--Snow King/Spring Creek, 1994-2004 (Box USA52)
    - Jackson Hole--Maps, 2003 and undated (Box USA52)
    - Targhee, 1977-2004 (Box USA52)
    - Yellowstone, 1989-2002 and undated (Box USA52)
- Large Format Items, 1956-2005 and undated; 12; 4 boxes
  - General, 229
    - Hotel directory--Mandarin Oriental, 1992 (Box OVS1)
    - International Expeditions catalog, 2005 (Box OVS1)
  - Specialty Vacations, 230
    - Golf--Jerry Quinlan's Celtic Golf, undated (Box OVS1)
    - Rafting/Kayak--Outdoor Adventure River Specialists (OARS), 2005 (Box OVS1)
    - Sailing/Yachts--Beacon Bay Charters, undated (Box OVS1)
  - Africa, 231
    - Kenya--Map, 1972 (Box OVS1)
    - Kenya--Nairobi--New Stanley Hotel, 1967 (Box OVS1)
    - Morocco--Kasbah Tamadot (Richard Branson), 2005 (Box OVS1)
    - South Africa--Palace of the Lost City at Sun City, undated (Box OVS1)
    - South Africa--Sun City, 1994 (Box OVS1)
    - South Africa--Ulusaba Game Reserve (Richard Branson), 2004 (Box OVS1)
  - Asia, 232
    - General--Travcoa--Orient/China/India, 2002 (Box OVS1)
    - Burma/Myanmar--New World Inya Lake Hotel, 1996 (Box OVS1)
    - India--Cox & Kings India and Beyond, 2005 (Box OVS1)
    - Thailand--Information sheet, undated (Box OVS1)
  - Canada, 233
    - Royal Canadian Pacific Railroad, 2006 (Box OVS1)
  - Central America, 234
    - Costa Rica--Hotels/ecotourism, undated (Box OVS1)
    - Panama--SITMAR Cruises, 1975 (Box OVS1)
  - Europe, 235
    - General--Pegasus Riding Holidays (Firm), 1995 (Box OVS1)
    - France--Basque country, undated (Box OVS1)
    - France--Chateaux and hotels, 1960-1997 and undated (Box OVS1)
    - France--Flaneries-Bourges, undated (Box OVS1)
    - Greece--Five Star Greece villas and yachts, undated (Box OVS1)
    - Italy--Hotels, undated (Box OVS1)
    - Italy--Hotels--Baglioni, 2002 (Box OVS1)
    - Italy--Florence--Villa d'Este, 2005 (Box OVS2)
    - Italy--Lazio region spas, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Italy--Sardinia/Sicily (Palermo) tourist information, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Monte Carlo--Le Metropole Palace, 2002 (Box OVS2)
    - Scandinavia--Sweden--Stockholm, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Spain--Hotels, 1984 and undated (Box OVS2)
    - Switzerland--Geneva--Tourist office packet, 1990 (Box OVS2)
    - Switzerland--Gstaad--Grand Park Hotel, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Switzerland--Lake Geneva and Matterhorn region packet, 1999 (Box OVS2)
    - Switzerland--Luzerne Bureau of Tourism, 1990 (Box OVS2)
    - United Kingdom--General--Creme de la Creme, 1985 (Box OVS2)
    - United Kingdom--England--Cotswold House Hotel, undated (Box OVS2)
    - United Kingdom--Scotland--Old Course Hotel, 2002 (Box OVS2)
  - Mexico, 236
    - Guia Ilustrada de la Ciudad de Mexico (in Spanish), undated (Box OVS2)
  - Pacific Region, 237
    - Australia--Northern Territory/Outback, undated (Box OVS2)
    - New Zealand--Air New Zealand New Business to a New Continent, undated (Box OVS2)
    - New Zealand--Farm Holidays--Paratiho Farms, 2004 (Box OVS2)
    - Papua New Guinea--Information sheet, undated (Box OVS2)
  - South America, 238
    - General--Seafaring the Strait of Magellan (Myra Waldo for Town & Country), undated (Box OVS2)
    - Brazil--Rio de Janeiro hotels, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Chile--Hotel directory, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Venezuela--Avensa Airlines Comunica (Newsletter), undated (Box OVS2)
  - United States, 239
    - Arizona--Grand Canyon bulletin, 1981 (Box OVS2)
    - California--Article on John Muir (Chicago Tribune), 1990 Jan. 14 (Box OVS2)
    - California--Los Angeles--Four Seasons Hotel, 2004 (Box OVS2)
    - California--Sequoia/Kings Canyon (NPS bulletins), 1990-1992 (Box OVS2)
    - Georgia--Calloway Gardens, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Hawaii--Maui Four Seasons, 1991 (Box OVS2)
    - Montana--Papoose Creek Lodge, 2002 (Box OVS2)
    - New York--Metropolitan Museum, undated (Box OVS2)
    - Pennsylvania--Pocmont, 1960s (Box OVS2)
  - General, 240
    - Austen-Lehman Adventures catalog, 2005 (Box OVS3)
    - Bike Riders Tours catalog, 2005 (Box OVS3)
    - Overseas Adventures TravelWorld of Discovery catalog, 2005 (Box OVS3)
    - Student Travel Society poster, undated (Box OVS3)
  - Asia, 241
    - Singapore Tourism News, 2002 Jan./Feb. (Box OVS3)
  - Central America, 242
    - Belize--Magnum Report, 1995 (Box OVS3)
    - Guatemala--Facil-Easy Guatemala, 1979 (Box OVS3)
  - Europe, 243
    - Austria--Austria Today (Frederic Morton for Holiday), 1950s (Box OVS3)
    - Belgium--Belfort Hotels map Bruges, undated (Box OVS3)
    - France--France Magazine, 1985-1986 Winter (Box OVS3)
    - France--Homes Away (Butterfield & Robinson), 1992 (Box OVS3)
    - France--Overseas Adventure Travel barge cruise catalog, 2005 (Box OVS3)
    - Italy--Cortina--Cristallo Hotel, undated (Box OVS3)
    - Scandinavia--Finland tourist board magazine, 2005 (Box OVS3)
    - Scandinavia--Sweden travel bulletin, 1997 (Box OVS3)
  - South America, 244
    - General--Latin Travel Review (cover article on Antarctica), 1988 (Box OVS4)
    - General--The Good Neighbor Newsletter (Moore-McKormack Lines/S.S. Argentina), 1966 (Box OVS4)
    - Argentina--maps, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Chile--Maps, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Venezuela--Map of Estado Merida, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Venezuela--Tourist information, undated (Box OVS4)
  - United States, 245
    - General--Chicago Sun Times section on natural adventure travel, 1997 May 25 (Box OVS4)
    - Alaska--Alaska Wilderness Explorations schedule, 1987 (Box OVS4)
    - Florida--Fla/USA advertising supplement (includes advertisements for Song Airlines), 2004 (Box OVS4)
    - Hawaii--Maps, 1956-1984 (Box OVS4)
    - Illinois--Illinois Road Tours advertising supplement, 1992 (Box OVS4)
    - Michigan--Grand Hotel newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box OVS4)
    - New England Group Tour Magazine, 1991 Summer (Box OVS4)
    - North Carolina--Pinehurst News & Views, 2001 Winter (Box OVS4)
    - Oregon--Tourist information, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Carlsbad/Guadelupe MountainsThe Capitan Reef, 1993-1994 Winter (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Grand Canyon, 1990-1994 (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Sequoia/Kings CanyonSequoia Bark, 1992 Aug. (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Sequoia/Kings CanyonBackcountry Basics, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Yellowstonearticles, 1987-2003 and undated (Box OVS4)
    - Parks--Yosemite, 1992-1996 (Box OVS4)
    - South Carolina--Spoleto Festival, 2003 (Box OVS4)
    - Texas--Flying L Ranch, undated (Box OVS4)
    - Texas--Lake Austin Spa, 2002 (Box OVS4)
    - Utah--Article on Saltair (Bob Silver), undated (Box OVS4)
    - Wisconsin--Chula Vista/Lake Geneva, 1997-2004 (Box OVS4)